electronicbeats.net 2017-11-26

# Privacy Policy – Telekom Electronic Beats

Data protection and data security for customers and users have a high priority for the entire Deutsche Telekom Group. We therefore attach great importance to the protection of personal data in all business processes. More about our privacy policy principles, which are valid throughout many Deutsche Telekom companies, can be found in the Privacy Code of Conduct of Deutsche Telekom (142 KB, *.pdf).

This privacy statement explains what kind of information is collected at the Deutsche Telekom Group during a visit to one of our Web sites and how we use this information. However, this does not apply to Web sites of companies which do not belong to the Group, even if they have a link to this or any other Web site of aDeutsche Telekom AG company. Should you wish to receive information on the collection and processing of personal data at specific companies of the Deutsche Telekom Group, please contact these companies directly or use our contact form.

##### Collection and processing of personal data

For the purpose of system security, when you visit our Web sites, our Web server temporarily registers the domain name or the IP address of the requesting computer as well as the date of access, the file request of the client (file name and URL), the HTTP response code and the Web site from which you are visiting us, and the number of bytes transferred during the session. We might also, in some cases, store some information in the form of ‘cookies’ on your PC so that we can optimize our Web site according to your preferences. We will not collect any other personal data such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address unless you provide this information voluntarily, e.g., when placing an online order for a product or service, a survey, a competition, or a request for information. Personal data collected during a visit to our Web site is processed exclusively in accordance with the legal provisions of the country in which the respective company is headquartered.

##### Use and forwarding of personal data

We will use your personal data exclusively for the technical administration of the Web site and to meet your wishes and requests. Only in cases in which you have given us prior consent do we also use this data for product-related surveys and marketing purposes, but only to the extent needed in each specific case. We will not disclose any data to government agencies except where required by law. Our employees and business offices are obligated to treat the data as confidential.

##### Customer‘s decision

The companies of Deutsche Telekom AG like to contact customers to provide them with information about special offers and news on products and services. If you register on our Web site or place an order for our products and services, you will be asked to indicate whether you would like to receive advertising information directly. Irrespective of your consent, it goes without saying that, as a Deutsche Telekom customer, you will continue to be notified of any important changes relating to existing service agreements (e.g., rate changes).

##### Freedom of information

Upon written request, the respective company of the Deutsche Telekom Group will inform you of the personal data stored on you (e.g., name, address).

##### Security

We have taken extensive technical and operational precautions to protect the personal data retained by us against unauthorized access and misuse. Our security procedures are revised regularly and adapted to reflect technological progress.

##### Contacts

Should you wish any data to be corrected or deleted, or have any other questions or suggestions on data protection, please get in touch with us.

##### GeoLite Database

This product includes GeoLite2 data created by MaxMind, available from [http://www.maxmind.com](http://www.maxmind.com/).
